HARI PRASAD SANJEL

Storgata 79, 0182 Oslo, Norway
Tlf: +47 46344530
harisanjel@gmail.com
LinkedIn | GitHub | Portfolio Site



Summary

Motivated and detail-oriented front-end developer with over 2 years of experience at ProActive Developers Pvt. Ltd. specializing in creating responsive and user-friendly web applications. Committed to continuous learning and eager to solve complex problems and eventually contribute to team.

Key Competencies

- Programming Language: Python, JavaScript, SQL
- Web Development: HTML, CSS (Bootstrap, Tailwind, Material UI), JavaScript (ReactJS)
- Tools: Postman, Git, Figma

Professional Experience

Junior Frontend Web Developer, ProActive Web Developers, Kathmandu, Nepal June 2020 – July 2022

- Converting design mock-ups into functional web pages using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript in collaboration with design team
- Implementing responsive design by using CSS frameworks like Bootstrap or Tailwind CSS
- Ensuring cross-browser compatibility
- Identifying and fixing bugs in front-end code
- Learning and applying React.js, Material-UI, Git, RESTful APIs
- Participating in team meetings and brainstorming sessions to share progress, challenges, and exchange knowledge and ideas
- Support senior developers by handling routine tasks and minor projects
- Taking on additional responsibilities as needed

Teacher Assistant (Bachelor, Technology and Society), Oslo Metropolitan University, Oslo Aug 2023 – Dec 2023

- Developed and maintained course website, ensuring a user-friendly experience for students.
- Created interactive web-based tutorials and learning modules using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Provided technical support and troubleshooting for online course materials and resources.
- Collaborated with faculty to integrate new web technologies and manage content with Git.

Portfolio Projects

Personal Portfolio (HTML, CSS, JavaScript)

GitHub | Live Preview

■ FATE – Consultancy Website (React.js, Tailwind)

GitHub | Live Preview

Markdown Previewer (React.js)

GitHub | Live Preview

Random Quote Generator (React.js, API)

GitHub | Live Preview

Education

Aug 2022 – June 2024 Master of Applied Computer and Information Technology

Institution: Oslo Metropolitan University, Oslo, Norway

Major Subject: Universal Design of Information and Communication Tech.

Aug 2011 – Jan 2014 Master of Science in Information Technology

Institution: Sikkim Manipal University Distance Education, India
Subjects: OOP, Operating System, Database Management System

Relevant Certifications

- Responsive Web Design, freeCodeCamp, 5 Aug, 2024
- Front End Development Libraries, freeCodeCamp, 4 Aug, 2024
- Data Analysis with Python, freeCodeCamp, 9 Sep, 2023
- Javascript Algorithms and Data Structures, freeCodeCamp, 23 Aug, 2023
- Complete Python Mastery by Code with Mosh, serial no: cert_mzgy28xz
- Diploma in Computer Software from Milestone Institute Pvt. Ltd., Kathmandu Nepal
 15 Sep 2009 14 Mar 2010

Language

English: Fluent Norwegian: Intermediate (B1) Hindi: Fluent

References

+47 672 38 469

Ole Sneltvedt Barun Gautam

University Lecturer Managing Director

Oslomet University ProActive Developers and Business Solution Pvt.

ole.sneltvedt@oslomet.no Ltd. Naxal, Kathmandu

+977-01-4526893, +977-9851012337

info@proactivedevelopers.com